(Howard:)Our eyes locked over the pickled herring.
(Howard:)We never meant for it to happen.
(Raj:)One day, I hold a great ball
for the president of France.
(Raj:)But the rabbits,
they hate me and don't come.
I'm embarrassed, so I eat all the lettuce
in the world and make them watch.
(Leonard:)People could call me Angie.
[IN NEW YORK ACCENT]
"Yo, Angie. How's it going?"
(Howard:)To this day,
I can't look at pickled herring...
(Howard:)...without being aroused and ashamed.
(Howard:)Oh, cousin Jeanie.
[PENNY SIGHS]
(Penny:)Could you please drive a little faster?
(Sheldon:)Oh, I think we're going sufficiently fast.
[ENGINE KNOCKING]
(Sheldon:)-What's that?
-Nothing.
(Penny:)-The engine does that sometimes.
-It can't be nothing.
The "check engine" light is on.
We need a service station.
The light's been on
since I bought the car.
(Sheldon:)All the more reason to consult
with a mechanic before it explodes.